Thank you for watching.
Thanks for watching.
This time, we will be talking about Morning Musume。 Stay, this time with Morning Musume。 13's Mei Yamazaki and
Rui Hiromoto from Ochanomizu.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
Project 25th Anniversary Concert has just finished.
At the time of this recording, it is still just before the concert.
I'm going to be in charge of the back dance of Sayumi Michishige and Rena Tanaka as they put on makeup for their big eyes,
They are performing right in front of us.
I would like to dance as much as I can while watching them and learning a lot.
You have a prime position, don't you?
That's right.
I, Yamazaki, have opportunities to perform with various senior OG members,
I myself have never performed with them at all, so I am very nervous.
Speaking of the 25th anniversary, on the 30th of last month, Morning Musume。 15 Best Selection Jean 25th Anniversary was released last month.
This album includes the latest new songs and 2 songs that represent Morning Musume。 This album contains the latest new songs and a few versions of Morning Musume。
I, Yamazaki, am singing a little bit of "Love" with Okamura Nobori-chan and Sakurai Rio-chan,
I was so happy when I heard that the three of us were going to sing together, and I studied a lot of videos of our seniors performing,
But we did our best without forgetting our own style.
It was a lot of fun. I had a lot of fun while recording.
And Morning Musume。 23 will start Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn NEVER ENDING SHINE SHOW will start on September 16.
This tour is the first tour for the 17th term members,
And for Sei Fukumura, it is her last tour,
This tour is a combination of the first and the last,
I hope we can work hard and make lots of memories until the end of the tour.
Ochanomaha will start its live tour 2023 "Our hometown is Japan" on October 7.
This will be Ochanoma's first live house tour in all 47 prefectures of Japan,
We are all very enthusiastic and will do our best.
Please take a look at this video.
Please enjoy!Come on in!
Bad Boys Bad Boys Bad Boys Bad Boys
You're not enough!
I'm a real Nice Body Body
Party Party Party I'd step on my own feet
Not just... Not just...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ah Ah Ah, if it's hot, cool it down, it's good
Everybody Party Party if you're lonely
Nobody knows
When does love last?
Dynamite
Love is Dynamite
No matter how invincible you are, love is a reflection
I shouldn't be this nice to you
A Bright Future
Hope for a job
Wow Wow Wow
The future of Japan is wow wow wow
The world envies you Yeah
Yeah!
Let's fall in love
Wow Wow Wow Wow
Dance!
Dancing all the night
I don't know, I just can't get enough
I want you to love me everywhere
I'm not too shy to tell you myself.
Wow, we're the perfect couple
Woo, I've always wanted to be Everybody Party PartyWoo The Everybody Party Party of Your Dreams
Everyone is unaware of it
Woo Love is the pitfall of dreams
Mystery Love is a Mystery
Woo
That's not natural
This is life
But if you're good at it
I'll be happy
Even on this day
A life of infection
Wow, wow, wow
Your smile
Wow, wow, wow, wow
The world envies you
Hey, hey, hey, hey
I got dreams.
You do, don't you?
Wow, wow, wow, wow
Dance!
Dancing all of the night
Everybody, come on, let's get high!
One more time, high!
Love love love love marshmallow
WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW
DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB DUB
YEAH YEAH YEAH YEAH YEAH
love love love bag trip
WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW
LOVE LOVE LOVE IS SO WONDERFULLOVE LOVE LOVE IS SO WONDERFUL
surely this day is now
WOW WOW WOW WOW
The World Turns Inside Out
YEAH YEAH YEAH YEAH YEAH
Let's fall in love
WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW
GIRLS!
Dancing all of the night
Steal everyone already
WOW WOW WOW WOW
You and me both
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW
Dance!
Dancing all the night
WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW
WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW
Having fun? Watch the rest of the show!
Morning Musume。 23's Yamatsuki Mate
Ruri Hiromoto of Ochanoma presents Halo! stay!
From here, I'd like to talk a little about each other.
I'll ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and just answer them temp well and quickly.
I'll do my best!
What does autumn mean to you, Ruri?
The fall of physical education.
What hair and makeup trends have you been noticing lately?
I have a square hair iron, so I want to use it to curl my hair.I have a square hair iron and I want to use it to curl my hair.
What do you always keep in mind for singing?
Singing every day without fail so that my performance does not decline.
What is your favorite thing about Hiroshima Prefecture, where you are from?
I love the Hiroshima Toyo Cup.
I can wear the Cup uniform from my house to the stadium.
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year.
Which song would you like to try your baton twirling skills to?
Masayume by Tsubaki Factory
Recently, I've been thinking about square hair irons.
Cotes are round, aren't they?
but it's square.
It's not round, but it's square.
so it's easy to curl.
I've never seen it before.
I'll try it sometime.
I'll try it someday!
I'm good at baton twirling.
That's great.
Why do you want to do it in Masayume?
Originally, the music for the competition goes at a very fast tempo.
So I thought it would be easier for me to dance if the tempo was similar to that.
I wanted to make my own choreography.
You make your own choreography?
I'd love to see it!
Thank you very much.
Questions for Ms. Yamazaki after the VTR
Hallo! STE.
Tsubaki Factory IT'S MY LIFE September 27 onsail
Tsubaki Factory or not, Sept. 27 On SailOr Tsubaki Factory, Sept. 27 onsail.
Hallo! Sta.
Next I would like to ask Mr. Yamazaki a question from me.
I'll do my best.
Morning Musume。 Instagram on the 4th anniversary of your joining What kind of posts do you make?
I introduce sweets in my story Three months have passed since the new member joined the group.
In a word, how would you describe your current role in the group? I give energy to everyone with sweets and panda power.
Morning Musume。's "Best Selection The 25th Anniversary: Show Yourself" was released on August 30. Which song do you think is your highlight?
I'm here! What do you keep in mind during live performances? I am aware of each and every audience member.
Which Hello Project song would you like to perform someday? Fiesta Fiesta by Juice Juice.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to dig a little deeper into what you're interested in.
Yes, I have to take a video of the snacks I've been eating lately and my snack of the day, and put it in a 15-second story with my voice.
It's a bit difficult, but I'm trying my best.
Today I bought two more of those melon soda flavored okoshi because they were so good.
Thank you very much.
And what you try to do during the show, it is important to look at various places, isn't it?
Yes, that's right. I try to look at the audience in high places, such as on the second or third floor,
Sometimes I can't see much of the audience at the end of the stage,
You're here! I would point and wave to them as if to say, "Hey, it's you!
I thought that if I just waved my hand, it would be hard to tell who I was waving to,
So I try to be conscious of various types of waving.
I am learning a lot. Thank you very much.
Halo! Ste.
I'm Kiimiyabi Matsuyaki. This is Sachi Hirayama from Angeleum.
I will do my best to make delicious pork piccata. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
So, what shall we make this time?
Today's dish is pork piccata.
Pork Piccata.
It is an Italian dish.It is an Italian dish.
Simply put, it's like a thin pork cutlet without breadcrumbs,
This is important.
It's important.
Oh no!
This is bad!
So, doctor, where do we start this time?
Let's start with the meat.
I'm going to cook the cheese rather than the meat.
It's true that when it's done, it's more cheese than meat. Completely.
A lot of cheese.
And today, we're grilling it with butter.
Absolutely delicious!
It's super hot.
It's good.
If you cook it in a frying pan over high heat, the butter will start to burn where you put it.
It will melt on the inside,
So put the butter in before you turn on the heat.
Melt the butter well.
Turn it around.
When it's melted and bubbling,
Please give a glance to Natsuyaki-san.
I understand. I have a point there.
I think it's about time.
Give me a look.
Sent!
This is the Miyamizu point.
Keep the foam coming out of the butter.
Keep.
This is it. You whisk it up.This is it. You make bubbles.
Now you have a lot of bubbles.
So, I'm going to reduce the vigor a little bit.
Now it's foaming up a lot.
The teacher will hold it for you,
So, put a lot of pork on it.
It's starting.
Put it on the pork.
It's all gooey.
Oh no.
Now only the outside has butter,
I don't think it's right underneath.
Let it float a little bit,
Let the butter get underneath.
Maybe it's time to give it back.
Let it rise a little bit,
See how it browns.
It looks good.
It's good. It's ready.
Wait until it hardens,
When it hardens, put it on top or pull it over.
Not yet. It's no good if we do it now.
When it's half hardened,
Put it on the side.
Put this one here, too.
If you stick them together, you can make a batter.
The meat is so thin,
It cooks quickly,
So you don't need to use a high heat,
The important thing is to cook the skin nicely.It is important that the skin be nicely cooked.
This one is probably undercooked.
If you cook it any longer, it will burn.
I think it's ready to go.
I can't wait to see the balsamic sauce on this.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, I'm going to serve it right away.
Now, the carrot marinade that I marinated earlier is nice and wilted.
I'm going to put it out here.
If you put a little bit of water in, it's hard for the oil to blend with it.
So, please use this lightly to remove the water.
That's a lot of water.
It's gone, right?
At this point, you can taste it again.
Taste it again to see how much salt is in it, and if it's too salty.
If it's too salty, add a little more vinegar.
Balance the saltiness and acidity.
I think it's already delicious.
Delicious carrots!
"Delicious carrots." That's a normal thing to say.
Is it good?
Is it salty?
Salty. Not too salty.
It's gentle.
It doesn't have much texture.
Maybe a little more salt.
I'll add a little, doctor.
Yes, sir.
Mix it up.
White wine today?You're making white wine today?
Yes, sir.
It's very strong.
That's right.
Something with acidity.
And balance it out.
Yes.
And then, mix it again.
And a tablespoon of olive oil
It's so easy to do, it's good.
This feels good for about a week
Convenient, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I think it's good.
I want to make the tomatoes a little bit rounder.
I want to cut them straight, and after cutting, I want to cut the core here, so I'll cut them at an angle.
And then cut it into bite-size pieces.
It's almost done, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Four more to go.
I'm going to have them put them in a tight pile here.
Half of it should be enough.
You could use half of the tomatoes, too.
All of them might be a little much.
The trick to serving the carrot rappe is to make it as big as possible.
The trick to serving the carrot rapé is to make it stand up as high as possible.
It's got a core.
I think it's good.
Beautiful
And two pieces of meat, one after the otherAnd two more pieces of meat!
So big!
Wow!
Olive oil!
Cute cow
And like 5 lines coming out here
It's on the vegetables too.
So you're trying to get around as much as possible.
Yeah, that's right.
If it's thick, it's not very cool.
Thin as much as possible.
I'd like to practice here once.
Practice.
If you think it looks good, go ahead.
If you think it looks good, go ahead and do it.
But if you do it with the feeling that this is my work
It will be more convincing.
It's totally convincing.
That's it.
I like it.
Wait a minute.
It better be close.
Thank you very much.
Here we go, doctor.
Look at that.
Here we go.
Just like before.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's good.
A little too thin.A little too thin.
Can I try again?
Yes, ma'am.
Is that okay?
Yes, it's done.
Can you point it at the camera, please?
Yes, sir. Pork Piccolo.
Yay!
Pork Piccata is ready!
How about you, Mr. Hirayama?
Yes, it's the first time I've made something like this, so...
This is the first time I've made something like this.
I was so nervous.
I put a lot of cheese.
The color here is really nice.
I can't wait to eat it.
And the balsamicos sauce was a nice touch.
I'm glad I touched it like this.
Well, let's eat it now!
Bon appétit!
Here you go.
I like cheese, so it's really delicious.
I put a lot of cheese in it, so the crunchy part of the cheese is just right.
The meat is very tender and delicious.
I also chopped the carrots into small pieces at the beginning,
Please try the carrots too.
I hope you will try the carrots as well.Yeah!
Yeah!
Okay, this is good.
I shredded them because they weren't evenly sized,
It has a lot of different textures and crunchiness,
It's a marinade, but it's not too acidic, so it's easy to eat and delicious.
How did you like it? What did you think of it this time?
Yes, it was very good. I usually don't cook much,
I usually say that I am afraid of cooking,
But Ms. Natsuyaki and the teacher were very kind and easy to work with,
And it was so delicious, I was able to make something that was right in the middle of my tastes,
That was great. That was great.
I hope I can make many more at home for myself and my family.
Thank you very much.
If there are any dishes you would like to try again,
Please come on Hello Kitchen.
Yes, of course. Of course.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now, Hello Kitchen.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!
It looked so delicious.
It looked delicious. It was stylish.
It was stylish.
Yes, it was.
Have you done any cooking lately, Ruri?
You haven't?
No. I don't cook anymore.
That's right.That's right.
I don't cook much.
So, is there anything you would like to cook?
Not cooking, but I would like to cook fish.
That sounds cool.
That's cool. Do you like fish?
I love fish. I like tuna, sea bream, and flatfish.
I love it.
That's great.
Would you like to give it to someone else?
I want to make a house of sweets,
Oh, that's a dream.
I want to build a big house of sweets, big enough for me to live in,
I want to spend a whole day there and eat a lot of sweets at the end of the day.
That sounds great.
It's not cooking, but I'd like to do it.
Hallo! STE!
Next up was the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Project has many lyrics that touch my heart,
Do you have a favorite lyric?
Yes, I like the lyrics of "Do It Now," "I don't want to stand still because I can only go forward step by step in life,
You only live once, and time is passing by quickly.
I love the lyrics because I think it is a lyric that sticks in my mind that we should not stand still because we are lost, but rather, we should run straight and go for it.
I love the lyrics.
I, Yamazaki, think that this weekend is a three-day weekend for some of you,
I have a lyric that I think is perfect for such a holiday,
The lyrics are about the singer, Sazaye Knight, who is making the most of her daily life,
The lyrics are about forgetting about school, work, and all the other things you have to do every day,
I think the lyrics are about forgetting the daily school, work, and other things that you have to work hard for and having a good time.
So, I hope you will listen to this song and get into the groove.So I hope you will listen to this song and get into the groove.
Now please watch the VTR.
Please watch the VTR.
Here it is!
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart!
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of the songs of Hello!
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Riko Yamagishi, will be in charge.
Now, I will make an announcement. Here it is.
I've never been able to be dexterous and have always been moving left and right.
I find myself carrying a heavy bag on my back
I couldn't even think of putting it down because it was filled with precious promises and thoughts.
It's a cute iron heart lyric, and it's a bit long, but the chorus is the chorus of the song,
I really love this song, and I even sang it at my birthday event. I even sang it at my birthday event. Yes!
I like the lyrics too, but the flirtatiousness? I love the chirpiness of Cute's live performance, and I also love the lyrics,
I love the chirpiness of Cute's live performance, and I also love the lyrics. I'm clumsy, so I couldn't be dexterous, and when I first came here, I was always doing too many things,
I was also under a bit of pressure since I became the leader, and I felt that the lyrics here are very much linked to that.
The important promises and thoughts are the thoughts of Tsubaki and the members, and the leader was able to do his best because everyone was there for him.
Oh! I love it!
When I heard this song, I thought, "Wow, what nice lyrics!
It's a very nice interpretation.
I'm sorry to everyone who likes ℃-ute. I interpreted it on my own.
No, no, but there is a link between the two, isn't there? Yes, I think so.
I'm sure that if you listen to the song, you will find that it is quite applicable to you. The lyrics seem to be applicable to everyone, and they are wonderful.
There are a lot of positive lyrics in this song, and I like just that one line about believing in yourself being invincible,
I think it is important to believe in something, and I also believe in the members, and I think it applies to me as I am active as a member of the group, so I really like the lyrics.
I really love this song, and I hope everyone will listen to it.
I really love this song, and I hope everyone will listen to it as much as possible. Bye bye.
Morning Musume。 23's Mei Yamazaki
This is Lili Hiromoto from Ochanoma, the place where you can find us on the Halo! Ste.Halo, brought to you by Lili Hiromoto of Ochanomizu! Ste.
Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year in 2023.
Here, we would like to introduce some of the music videos we have selected from the 25 years of their songs, with great costumes and makeup.
I like the music video of I WISH,
There are two versions of I WISH, the original music video and the Morning Musume。 22 version,
In the original music video, the older members take off their jackets at the same time,
The original music video has a scene where the older members take off their jackets at the same time, but the '22 version has them on,
That's how we are going to make the future of Morning Musume。 That's how we are going to make the future of Morning Musume,
I really like the way they are showing that we are going to make the future of Morning Musume Musume and do our best,
I also like the costumes, of course, and I thought it was wonderful that they used such costumes in the performance.
Alone and a little bored at night
I'm the only one who's lonely.
It's so silly and funny.
I got a text message
For some reason I can't stop crying
Oh, thank you
You know me better than anyone.
You know me.
I have to believe in you more than anyone.
Hey, you have to believe in me more than anyone.
Life is great.
See, you meet someone, you fall in love
Oh, it's wonderful Oh, it's crazy
I can laugh and cry
The next music video I would choose with great costumes and makeup is "Ai no Kedamono".
I think the strength of the song is really expressed in the costumes and makeup,
In addition to that, the location of the music video is really beautiful, and the power of the music video, your dancing, and the visuals are very powerful,
I really like the way the power of the music video is conveyed to the viewer through the screen.
And I think this song is my favorite out of all the songs I chose.
I want to make this song my favorite song.I want this song to be my favorite song.
I want to make this song my favorite song.
I want to make this song my favorite song
Love us, we're so promising
In the first place, the earth is the weak and the strong
If you use the actual machine and feel it, and our eyes meet
See, I'm already hooked
I love you, promising us
We're on the verge of our first fiery encounter
We're both lonely and sensitive
I'll protect you so much, won't I?
Feel how strong we really are
Prepare yourself with the love you've got
Glad Quarter Sensory Encore
Thank you for all the fun memories of this summer.
Now, this is really the last song.
I miss you
Alone and a little bored at night
I'm the only one who misses you
It's so silly and funny
I got your mail
I don't know why I can't stop cryingI can't stop crying for some reason.
Thank you.
More than anyone.
You know me.
I have to believe in you more than anyone.
It's great to be in love, isn't it, Kazuo?
Meeting someone, falling in love.
In a wonderful universe.
You can laugh, you can cry.
Some days I'm afraid to talk to anyone.
But I have the courage to tell them about me. About me.
Because there will be sunny days, and then there will be rain.
And it'll all make sense one day.
Life is great.
See, it's always the same.
We'll find something that's the same.
Yeah, it's great.
Yeah, or someone else.
Let's find a way to find each other
Ah yeah
Cause there's a dream day
Cause it's gonna rain sooner or later
Someday it'll all make sense
Life goes on
It's great
You know, you meet someone.
You meet someone, you fall in love.
It's great.
You're crazy about it.I'm crazy about it.
I can laugh, I can cry.
Life is great
See, even if it's the same road we've always taken, we'll find something to do
That's great.
Oh, look who's here.
Let's find a way to meet someone
But I've always kept a smile on my face
For the ones you love
Let's do our best tomorrow!
Morning Musume。 23's Mei Yamazaki and
Ruri Hiromoto of Ochanomizu, and Ruri Hiromoto of Ochanomizu, will be presenting Halo! STE, presented by Mei Yamazaki of Morning Musume。
It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
Morning Musume。 21 Best Selection The 25th Anniversary is now on sale.
This album includes 2 or 3 versions of the songs,
You can listen to various songs, so please listen to it a lot.
Morning Musume。' 23 will start their fall tour this weekend on September 16.
This is the first tour for the 17th term members and the last tour for Sei Fukumura,
This is the last tour with 14 members.
I would like to do my best until the end of the tour.
The autumn tour will start on October 7.
We will visit the hometowns of all 10 members and other prefectures we have never been to before, so please look forward to the tour.
Morning Musume。 23 will perform at Inazuma Rock Fest 2023 on October 9.
We are looking forward to seeing you. I am sure that there will be many people who don't know Morning Musume。
I will also perform at the trainee presentation on September 17 and 18 at Ocha-no-Ma.
And on November 19, we will hold the Ochanoma community revitalization concert in Bizen City, Okayama Prefecture.
This will be the first time for Miku Nishizaki to perform at many events and pass tours in her hometown, Okayama Prefecture, so please come and visit us!
Hello! Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time we had Mei Yamazaki from Morning Musume。 23's Mei Yamazaki and Rui Hiromoto of Ocha-no-Ma.
Good bye.